Guide to the Records of the NYU TV and Media Services Video Recordings RG.38.16.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Video Recordings, 1993-2005; 219087
  - "Master Chef" Contest, 26 Feb 2007; cuid1094; 239016; 8 minidvs (Box 70)
  - Paul Farmer: Social Entrepreneurship in the 21st Century"= Social Reynolds Speaker Series, 8 May 2007; cuid1095; 239024; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - "The Artist in Residence" The Institute of African American Affair's, 17 Apr 2007; cuid1096; 239025; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - "Global Crisis in the Nursing Workforce", 1 Oct 2007; cuid1097; 239026; 2 minidvs (Box 70)
  - Presidential Welcome 2007, 27 Aug 2007; cuid1098; 239027; 1 minidvs (Box 70)
  - "Midwife Conversation" School of Nursing, 24 Aug 2007; cuid1099; 239028; 1 minidvs (Box 70)
  - "SMPTE NY" at Cantor Film Center, 6 Jun 2007; cuid1100; 239029; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - Steinhardt Faculty Concert, 10 Sep 2007; cuid1101; 239030; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - All Library Staff Meeting with Dean Carol Mandel, 31 May 2007; cuid1102; 239031; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - "Reality Show" program, 31 Aug 2007; cuid1103; 239032; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - Jason Stanyek Lecture, 11 May 2007; cuid1104; 239033; 19 minidvs (Box 70)
  - "Sustainable Agriculture" Fales Food Program, 25 Jul 2007; cuid1105; 239034; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Fazle Hasan, 21 Sep 2007; cuid1106; 239035; 2 minidvs (Box 70)
  - Master Chef Samples, 1 Jan 2007; cuid1107; 239036; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 70)
  - Welcome Week 2007, 31 Aug 2007; cuid1108; 239037; 5 minidvs (Box 70)
  - "Further Adventures in Legal" Law School, 20 Jun 2007; cuid1109; 239038; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - Global Mitigation, 25 Apr 2006; cuid1110; 239039; 2 minidvs (Box 70)
  - "Interview with Jaime" Video Art Interviews, 10 Oct 2007; cuid1111; 239040; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - VLAL Step-up B-Roll, 8 Oct 2007; cuid1112; 239041; 1 minidvs (Box 70)
  - "Global Public Health: Dead Mums Don't Cry", 9 oct 2007; cuid1113; 239042; 2 minidvs (Box 70)
  - "Where Farmers Grow" Fales Food Series, 11 Oct 2007; cuid1114; 239043; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi at the Greenburg Lounge, 12 Oct 2007; cuid1115; 239044; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - CAS's Parent's Event, 20 Oct 2007; cuid1116; 239045; 1 minidvs (Box 70)
  - Bio-Ethics Conference, 20 Oct 2007; cuid1117; 239046; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - Colloquium on the Supreme Court Case, 24 Oct 2007; cuid1118; 239047; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - Liberia Lecture, undated; cuid1119; 239048; 1 minidvs (Box 70)
  - The 8th Annual Lewis Burke Frumkes Lecture, 29 Oct 2007; cuid1120; 239049; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - The Ignaugural Jacob K. Javits Lecture, 29 Oct 2007; cuid1121; 239050; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - Social Entreprenuership in the 21st Century with J.B. Schramm, 30 Oct 2007; cuid1122; 239051; 2 minidvs (Box 70)
  - College of Nursing Studio Interviews, 2 Nov 2007; cuid1123; 239052; 2 minidvs (Box 70)
  - Steinhardt Jazz Symphony Anycast Shoot, 26 Oct 2007; cuid1124; 239053; 6 videocassettes (Box 70)
  - SCPS Media Talk in Tishman Auditorium, 7 Nov 2007; cuid1125; 239054; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - Rudin Center for Transporation Conference, 13 Nov 2007; cuid1126; 239057; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - Steinhardt Department of Music "Piano Inter-Studio", 19 Nov 2007; cuid1127; 239058; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - All University Sing, 9 Dec 1997; cuid1128; 240097; 2 videocassettes (Box 71)
  - The NYU Festival String Orchestra, 11 Mar 1998; cuid1129; 240098; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 71)
  - Yale Storm and Hot Pastrami, 4 Nov 1998; cuid1130; 240099; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 71)
  - Education Policy Breakfast "Black and White Acheivement", Unknown; cuid1131; 240100; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "Does Money Matter?", 22 Mar 2001; cuid1132; 240101; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "Closing the Achievement Gap", 13 Dec 2001; cuid1133; 240102; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "An Instructional Vision", 12 Dec 2001; cuid1134; 240103; 2 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "The Purpose of Education", 25 Mar 2002; cuid1135; 240104; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "Mathematics: Clear or Fuzzy?", 29 Apr 2003; cuid1136; 240105; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "Gender Implications", 5 Apr 2000; cuid1137; 240106; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Installation of the 15th President, 26 Sep 2002; cuid1138; 240107; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Bobst Library, 28 Apr 1998; cuid1139; 240108; 2 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 71)
  - President Oliva Promotes New York University TV, 8 Aug 1995; cuid1140; 240109; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 71)
  - Hang Blix: Disarming Iraq, 15 Mar 2004; cuid1141; 240110; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - "Critical Topics in Food" Fales Series, 17 May 2005; cuid1142; 240111; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - A Lecture with Helen Zia "Colliding into 2020", 5 October 2004; cuid1143; 240112; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Amy Goodman, 24 Feb 2004; cuid1144; 240113; 2 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Lewis Burke Frumkes Lecture in Philiosophy Noam Chomsky, 15 Nov 2004; cuid1145; 240114; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Bobst Library Anniversary, 16 Dec 2002; cuid1146; 240115; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Susana Baca, 15 July 2003; cuid1147; 240116; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Lewis Burke Frumkes Lecture in Philosophy Peter Singer, 17 Nov 2003; cuid1148; 240117; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - MIAP Speakers Series: Dan Streible, 19 Nov 2004; cuid1149; 240118; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Fales Library Series: Marvin Taylor, 12 Feb 2003; cuid1150; 240119; 2 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Hugh Masereld and Harry Belefonte in Conversation, 22 Feb 2005; cuid1151; 240600; 2 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Scholars and Artists Episode 1, 20 Jan 2005; cuid1152; 240601; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - David Wojnarowicz and Peter Hujar, 20 Sep 2005; cuid1153; 240603; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - John Kerry Lecture, 20 Sep 2004; cuid1154; 240604; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Wagner School, 11 Oct 2000; cuid1155; 240605; 1 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Charlie Rose Lecture, 21 Nov 2003; cuid1156; 240606; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Jay Oliva Portrait Unveiling, 5 May 2003; cuid1157; 240607; 1 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Fales Lecture Series "Up is up, But So Is Down", 26 Oct 2006; cuid1158; 240608; 1 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Robert Preston Tisch Dinner, 26 Jan 2006; cuid1159; 240609; 1 videocassettes (Box 71)
  - Skirball Center Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 2 Oct 2003; cuid1160; 240610; 1 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Skirball Center Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 2 Oct 2003; cuid1161; 243463; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - TV 37 Clone Music, undated; cuid1162; 240611; 1 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Kimmel Exterior Station ID, undated; cuid1163; 240612; 1 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Kimmel Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 11 Jun 2003; cuid1164; 240613; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Puck Building Dedication and Debate, 23 Sep 2004; cuid1165; 240614; 2 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Hannah Kohn Tabacco Use Lecture, 30 Oct 2001; cuid1166; 240615; 1 minidvs (Box 71)
  - SS Proleterka Reading by Feur Jaeggy, 9 Dec 2003; cuid1167; 240616; 2 minidvs (Box 71)
  - America and Islam in a Global World, 24 Jan 2002; cuid1168; 240617; 5 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 72)
  - America and Islam in a Global World, 24 Jan 2002; cuid1169; 243464; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 72)
  - Domestic and Family Violence in the 21st Century, 2 Feb 2001; cuid1170; 240618; 6 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 72)
  - Carol Gilligan "Understanding Gender", 5 Apr 2000; cuid1171; 240619; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 72)
  - NYU Development Dr. Epstein Surgery, 26 Oct 1995; cuid1172; 240620; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 72)
  - Harold Levy Lecture, 26 Apr 2000; cuid1173; 240621; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 72)
  - John Lang and Todd Gitlin, 1 Dec 1998; cuid1174; 240622; 4 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 73)
  - Spike Lee Black Genuis, 8 Oct 1998; cuid1175; 240623; 2 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 73)
  - Downtown Poetry Reading at Fales Library, 27 Oct 1998; cuid1176; 240625; 1 videocassettes (Box 73)
  - African American Trade Unions at Bobst Library, 10 Feb 2000; cuid1177; 240624; 2 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 73)
  - Dennis Cooper Panel, 2 Mar 2000; cuid1178; 240626; 2 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 73)
  - New York University TV Alumni Interview Brian Frazee, 26 Aug 1998; cuid1179; 240627; 7 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 73)
  - NYU Celebrates Africana Studies, 25 Sep 1998; cuid1180; 240628; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 73)
  - Carol Gilligan "Understanding Gender", 2 Apr 2000; cuid1181; 240629; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 73)
  - MCTP: Seminar Norm Fruchter, 30 Apr 2003; cuid1182; 240634; 2 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Women's Rights Conference, undated; cuid1183; 240658; 2 videocassettes (minidv) (Box 74)
  - "From Fundemental Principles to Selection Criteria" Barbara Goldsmith Preservation Lecture Series, Hal Erickson, 24 Jun 2002; cuid1184; 240635; 2 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Jack Schwartz Retirement Dinner, 29 Oct 2004; cuid1185; 240636; 1 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Securing America in the 21st Century, 9 Sep 2005; cuid1186; 240638; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Courant Institute Interviews, 6 Oct 2005; cuid1187; 240639; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - The End of Poverty, Jeffrey Sachs, 5 Oct 2005; cuid1188; 240640; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Critical Topics in Food: Luxury Dining, 20 Oct 2005; cuid1189; 240655; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Gertrude Belle Elion, 11 Oct 2005; cuid1190; 240656; 2 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Jenny Holzer "For the City", undated; cuid1191; 240657; 1 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Kimmel Opening Ceremony, 11 Jun 2003; cuid1192; 240660; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 74)
  - Graduate Studies Alumni Panel, 14 May 2005; cuid1193; 240661; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Amy Goodman Lecture, 1 Sep 2005; cuid1194; 240662; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Critical Topics in Food: Food Writers of Greenwich Village, 10 Mar 2006; cuid1195; 240663; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Culture and Communications, 1 Sep 2005; cuid1196; 240664; 1 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Visions of a Changing Theater, undated; cuid1197; 240665; 5 minidvs (Box 74)
  - The Moving Edge: The Place of Downtown Art in NYC, undated; cuid1198; 241106; 10 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - The Moving Edge: The Place of Downtown Art in NYC, undated; cuid1199; 243465; 1 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Simon Reynolds: Raw Footage, undated; cuid1200; 241107; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Downtown Show: Nightclubbing, n.d.; cuid1201; 241108; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - APA studies: Globalization and China Economic, 1 Sep 2006; cuid1202; 241109; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Neil Postman Symposium, undated; cuid1203; 241110; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - NYU Metro Regional Alumni Brooklyn Dodgers 1955, 15 Nov 2005; cuid1204; 241111; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Board of Trustees Dinner, 10 Apr 2005; cuid1205; 241112; 1 videocassettes (Box 74)
  - Lewis Burke Frumkes Lecture in Philosophy, 16 Nov 2005; cuid1206; 241113; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - The Reality Show, 24 Oct 2005; cuid1207; 241114; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - The National Conference for Community and Justice, 9 Feb 2006; cuid1208; 241115; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - MIAP The Moving Image: Texts as Iodes of Metadata, 28 Oct 2005; cuid1209; 241116; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Convocation in Honor of Gordon Brown and Alan, 14 Dec 2005; cuid1210; 241117; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Taking Journalism Seriously, 21 Apr 2006; cuid1211; 241118; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Dean's Day, 13 May 2006; cuid1212; 241119; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - NYC TVC Reel, undated; cuid1213; 241120; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Image of Ben Franklin As Seen by Himself, 3 Feb 2006; cuid1214; 241121; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Image of Ben Franklin As Seen by Himself, 3 Feb 2006; cuid1215; 243459; 1 minidvs (Box 74)
  - The Reality Show 2005, cuid1216; 241122; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Stern Panel Dicussion, 28 Oct 2005; cuid1217; 241123; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Security in Ghana, undated; cuid1218; 241124; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Raw Video: Downtown Show, 27 Jan 2006; cuid1219; 241125; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - "Ultraviolet", 18 Apr 2006; cuid1220; 241126; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Zukerman Forum 2006, 18 Apr 2006; cuid1221; 241127; 4 minidvs (Box 74)
  - National Public Policy Forum Debate, 22 Apr 2006; cuid1222; 241128; 4 minidvs (Box 74)
  - King Juan Carlos Center, 1 Dec 2005; cuid1223; 241129; 2 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Wagner Admissions Video, 11 Apr 2006; cuid1224; 241130; 1 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Leo Barsanili and Lehman Lecture, 11 Apr 2006; cuid1225; 241131; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Promo "Cribs" PSA, 12 Sep 2002; cuid1226; 241132; 1 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 1, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1227; 241139; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Season 3 Islam, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1228; 241140; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 5, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1229; 241141; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 7 Britain, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1230; 241142; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 9 Britain, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1231; 241143; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 10 Britain, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1232; 241144; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 12 France, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1233; 241145; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 14 United States, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1234; 241146; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 16 India, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1235; 241147; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 18 Japan, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1236; 241148; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008: Preliminary Rounds B-roll, 22 Feb 2008; cuid1237; 241149; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008, 22 Feb 2008; cuid1238; 241150; 4 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008 Finals, 10 Apr 2008; cuid1239; 241151; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008 Finals, 10 Apr 2008; cuid1240; 243460; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008 Panel, 22 Feb 2008; cuid1241; 241152; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 75)
  - Siemens Competition Program History, 4 Dec 2006; cuid1242; 241153; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Siemns Competition Awards Ceremony, 4 Dec 2006; cuid1243; 241154; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - September 11: Our University Remembers, 11 Sep 2006; cuid1244; 241155; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Robert Rosenblum Symposium, 14 Oct 2006; cuid1245; 241156; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Al Gore: Policy Address on Climate Change, 18 Sep 2006; cuid1246; 241157; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs Spotlights: Ann Morning, Perry Halkitis, 23 Aug 2005; cuid1247; 241158; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs Highlights Corrections, 10 Dec 2005; cuid1248; 241159; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs Promo, undated; cuid1249; 241160; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs: Ann Morning Rought Segments, undated; cuid1250; 241161; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs Highlights Promo, 9 Apr 2009; cuid1251; 241162; 1 videocassettes (Box 75)
  - President of Cyprus, 18 Sep 2009; cuid1252; 241163; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Metro Tech Education Meeting, 17 Jul 2006; cuid1253; 241164; 2 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Who Makes Policy on Africa? Raw Footage and Master Tapes, 17 Apr 2006; cuid1254; 241165; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Edward Wilson Lecture, 3 Jan 2007; DV; 241166; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Edward Wilson Lecture, 3 Jan 2007; cuid1255; 243461; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 75)
  - How to Get Into Translation Business, 24 Mar 2007; cuid1256; 241167; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - How to Get Into Translation Business, 24 Mar 2007; cuid1257; 243462; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 75)
  - Civil Rights Symposium, 28 Oct 2006; cuid1258; 241168; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Who's in Charge? Old Media, New Media, 8 Nov 2006; cuid1259; 241499; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - SCPS Marketing: Naomi Levine, 30 Apr 2007; cuid1260; 241500; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Chat with Financiers: Ajit Jain, 7 May 2007; cuid1261; 241502; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Wagner Intersections: Leslie Stahl Discussion, 1 Mar 2007; cuid1262; 241503; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Social Entreprenuership in the 21st Century, 1 Mar 2007; cuid1263; 241504; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Expanding the Vision: Recovery as a New, undated; cuid1264; 241505; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Trade and Africa Culture: Opening Remarks, 8 Nov 2006; cuid1265; 241514; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Trade and Africa Culture: The Millenium Village, 8 Nov 2006; cuid1266; 241515; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Trade an Africa Culture: African Agriculture, 8 Nov 2006; cuid1267; 241516; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Ourspace: DIY Media and the Future of Democracy, 9 Nov 2006; cuid1268; 241517; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Bill Drayton Lecture, 13 Oct 2006; cuid1269; 241518; 3 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Bill Drayton Lecture, 13 Oct 2006; cuid1270; 243457; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - MIAP Speaker Series: How to Find Film and Videos, 22 Sep 2006; cuid1271; 241519; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates, 20 Apr 2006; cuid1272; 241520; 4 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates, 20 Apr 2006; cuid1273; 243458; 4 dvd-r disks (Box 75)
  - Raw Stock Footage: Snow in Washington Square Park, 7 Mar 2007; cuid1274; 241521; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Hope Not Hate, 8 Sep 2002; cuid1275; 242861; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Hip Hop Journalism, 26 Oct 2004; cuid1276; 242862; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Grossberg Lecture, undated; cuid1277; 242863; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Robert McChesney Lecture, 11 Nov 2004; cuid1278; 242864; 2 videocassettes (Box 76)
  - Ultraviolet, undated; cuid1279; 242865; 3 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Campus Flash: Adutumn Fest, Ticket Central, 1 Sep 2002; cuid1280; 242866; 3 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Zantee Hou Interview for IRHC, undated; cuid1281; 242867; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Presidential Debate, 1 Nov 2004; cuid1282; 242868; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Beyond the Sea Segement CF, 1 Sep 2004; cuid1283; 242869; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Hayden Talent Show, undated; cuid1284; 242870; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Teach In: Who is Next? "North Korea and Beyond", 1 Apr 2003; cuid1285; 242876; 5 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Lost in Translation: Rough Final Cut PSA, undated; cuid1286; 242877; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - NYU TV Coming up Slate 2002, cuid1287; 242938; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - New York University Cribs 2003, cuid1288; 242939; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - University Stock Footage, undated; cuid1289; 242940; 4 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Women Who Cook for a Living in New York and Why, 11 Jul 2006; cuid1290; 242941; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Diet & Nutrition: Counseling a Dental Office, 8 Sep 2001; cuid1291; 242942; 3 minidvs (Box 76)
  - The Relationship of Health Promotion, 25 Oct 2001; cuid1292; 242943; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Real Estate, 24 Oct 2001; cuid1293; 242944; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Habib Kiote, 5 Oct 2001; cuid1294; 242945; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - HIPAA School of Social Work, 24 mar 2003; cuid1295; 242946; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Campus Flash: Gloria Cahill Interview, 21 Sep 2005; cuid1296; 242947; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Max Orestein: Hurricane Katrina Photography, 1 Nov 2005; cuid1297; 242948; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Campus Flash: Aviva Levine Interview, 26 Sep 2009; cuid1298; 242949; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Campus Flash: Bronfman Center Katrina Panel, 14 Sep 2005; cuid1299; 242950; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Senior Class Council c/o 2006, 3 Nov 2005; cuid1300; 242951; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Applefest, undated; cuid1301; 242952; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - The Matador movie press kit and interviews, undated; cuid1302; 242953; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - The Matador Brosnan Interview, undated; cuid1303; 242954; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Presidential Welcome 2004 (NYU class of 2008), cuid1304; 242955; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - TVC B-Roll, undated; cuid1305; 242956; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - NYU-TV Channel 15 Movie Promos F02/S03, undated; cuid1306; 242957; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - "25th Hour" Movie Promo and NYU TV Promo, 15 Sep 2003; cuid1307; 242958; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Bobst Interviews and Stand-Ups, 20 Jul 2001; cuid1308; 242959; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Bobst Stand-Ups and Exteriors, 20 Jul 2001; cuid1309; 242960; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Bobst Steadicam, 20 Jul 2001; cuid1310; 242961; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - "War Retold" Photographs of Vietnam by Serene Ford Northington, 8 Apr 2003; cuid1311; 242962; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - "War Retold" Photographs of Vietnam by Serene Ford Northington and her Mother, 16 Apr 2003; cuid1312; 242963; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Bobst B-Roll, 1 Jan 2002; cuid1313; 242964; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Campus Flash: Holiday Stress, 1 Dec 2002; cuid1314; 242965; 3 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Coles Writing, Center, and Bobst Archives Footage, 1 Jan 2001; cuid1315; 242966; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Lauren Acuna: New Channel 1, 1 Jan 2001; cuid1316; 242967; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - APA Artist Talk: Serene Ford Northington, 25 Feb 2003; cuid1317; 242968; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - SWANK Motion Pictures Promo, 1 Jan 2002; cuid1318; 242969; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - NYU Channel 15 Movie Promo, 1 Nov 2002; cuid1319; 242970; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Cooking Series: David Kamp, 6 Oct 2002; cuid1320; 242971; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - NYU Journalism: Jimmy Breslin Lecture, 18 Sep 2002; cuid1321; 242972; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Tisch School of Arts International Student Film, 28 Oct 2003; cuid1322; 242973; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Big Valentine's Fun Day, 1 Feb 2002; cuid1323; 242974; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - ABA Dialogue on Freedom Slate, 22 Oct 2002; cuid1324; 242975; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Vision Fest 2004, 1 Jan 2004; cuid1325; 242976; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Welcome to New York University, undated; cuid1326; 242977; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - NYU TV Logo Animations, undated; cuid1327; 242978; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Food Series: From Here to There, Food Chains, 19 Oct 2006; cuid1328; 242979; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Food Series: "What We Eat" by Marion Nestle, 4 May 2006; cuid1329; 242980; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - National Endowment for the Arts NEW 4, 15 Apr 2004; cuid1330; 242981; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - ITP Interactive Telecommunications Program, 13 May 2003; cuid1331; 242982; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - "Film School" IFC Docu-series Junket and Campus, 23 Aug 2004; cuid1332; 243060; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - NYU TV Christmas and Happy Holidays 2001 Promo, 9 Dec 2001; cuid1333; 243061; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - FBI Mon. Class Project 3, 1 Jan 2003; cuid1334; 243064; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Remarque Lecture: Mark Danner The Politics of the Forever War, 14 Nov 2006; cuid1335; 243065; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Inside NYU: Stand-up Founder's Memorial, 1 Jul 2005; cuid1336; 243066; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Inside NYU: Historic NYU, Campus Tour, 1 Jul 2005; cuid1337; 243067; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Inside NYU: Deutsches Haus, Ireland House, 27 Jul 2005; cuid1338; 243068; 1 minidvs (Box 76)